练习 1-42：描述性短语故事《丑小鸭》。下面这个著名故事
Exercise 1-42, Descriptive Phrase Story, The Ugly Duckling. The following well
被改写成只包含描述性短语。重读每个短语的第二个词。
-known story has been rewritten to contain only descriptions. Stress the second word
下面开始跟读故事。
of each phrase. Repeat after me. There's a mother duck. She lays three eggs. Soon
there are three baby birds. Two of the birds are very beautiful. One of them is
quite ugly. The beautiful ducklings make fun of their ugly brother. The poor thing
is very unhappy. As the three birds grow older, the ugly duckling begins to change.
His gray feathers turn snowy white. His gangly neck becomes beautifully smooth. In
early spring, the ugly duckling is swimming in a small pond in the backyard
of the old farm. He sees his shimmering reflection in the clear water. What a
great surprise! He's no longer an ugly duckling. He has grown into a lovely swan.